export const quiz = {
  mca:{
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?',
        choices: ['stringify()', 'parse()', 'convert()', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'stringify()',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?',
        choices: ['var', 'var and let', 'let', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'var and let',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
        choices: ['constant', 'var', 'let', 'const'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'const',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?',
        choices: [
          'document.write()',
          'console.log()',
          'window.alert',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },
    ],
  },
  mba: {
    topic: 'CAT level Questions',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'Five students, including Amit, appear for an examination in which possible marks are integers between 0 and 50, both inclusive. The average marks for all the students is 38 and exactly three students got more than 32. If no two students got the same marks and Amit got the least marks among the five students, then the difference between the highest and lowest possible marks of Amit is',
        choices: ['20', '24', '21', '22'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '20',
      },
      {
        question:
          'On day one, there are 100 particles in a laboratory experiment. On day n where n≥2 one out of every n particles produces another particle. If the total number of particles in the laboratory experiment increases to 1000 on day m then m equals',
        choices: ['16', '19', '17', '18'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '19',
      },
      {
        question:
          'If a and b are non-negative real numbers such that a+2b=6 then the average of the maximum and minimum possible values of (a+b) is',
        choices: [
          '4',
          '3.5',
          '4.5',
          '3',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '4.5',
      },
      {
        question: 'Manu earns ₹4000 per month and wants to save an average of ₹550 per month in a year. In the first nine months, his monthly expense was ₹3500, and he foresees that, tenth month onward, his monthly expense will increase to ₹3700. In order to meet his yearly savings target, his monthly earnings, in rupees, from the tenth month onward should be',
        choices: ['4200', '4350', '4300', '4400'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '4400',
      },
    ],
  },
  be: {
    topic: 'JEE mains level Questions',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'An interhalogen compound of Bromine reacts with excess of Fluorine to form?',
        choices: ['BrF5', 'BrF', 'BrF3', 'None of These'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'BrF5',
      },
      {
        question:
          'De-Broglie wavelength of alpha particle is the same as that of a proton moving with one-tenth of velocity as the speed of light. The ratio of K.E of proton to that of alpha particle is',
        choices: ['2:1', '4:1', '1:4', '4:3'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '4:1',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Number of Three digit Numbers which are divisible by 2 or 3 but not divisible by 7 is',
        choices: [
          '480',
          '650',
          '557',
          '534',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '557',
      },
      {
        question: 'Orthocenter of a Triangle whose vertices are (1,2), (2,1) and (3,1) is',
        choices: ['(1,1)', '(-1,1)', '(0,0)', '(1,-1)'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '(1,-1)',
      },
    ],
  },
  law: {
    topic: 'JEE mains level Questions',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'A property worth Rs. 25,00000/- was agreed to be sold for Rs. 8,00000/-. The mother of “X” moves the court for setting aside the agreement on the ground that “X” is a congenial “Idiot”. In this context, which one of the following is the correct answer?',
        choices: ['mother will succeed', 'mother is bound to execute the agreement', 'mother will not succeed', '“Idiot” can avoid the agreement'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'mother will succeed',
      },
      {
        question:
          'There is no fundamental right to –',
        choices: [
          'approach the Supreme Court to claim right to practice carry on business',
          'approach the High Court under Article 226 of the Constitution of India',
          'education',
          'freedom of press',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'approach the High Court under Article 226 of the Constitution of India',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Part IV A of the Indian Constitution deal with',
        choices: [
          'Directive Principles of state Policy',
          'Fundamental Rights',
          'Fundamental Duties',
          'Citizenship'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Fundamental Duties',
      },
      {
        question: ' Which one of the following is a fundamental duty of citizens?',
        choices: [
          'to sing National Anthem', 
          'to pay equal wages to men and women',
          'to organize village panchayats',
          ' guardians to provide for education to children between 6 and 14 years of age'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: ' guardians to provide for education to children between 6 and 14 years of age',
      },
    ],
  },
  }